Guide to the Frederick Fried Coney Island collection
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series II: Architectural and Design Drawings, 1847-1974 undated
  - Subseries II.3: Mapcase Drawings, 1911-1974 undated
    - Roller Coasters
      - General plan of tracks, circa 1900 (Box 15-J-9, Folder 4)
        J.R. Worcester, construction engineer; Loop Roller Coaster Company Photomechanical print, scale 1:96 Item is detached into two pieces: 321.1 = 17 5/8” x 23”, 321.2 = 18” x 22 ¾”
      - Typical cross sections, circa 1900 (Box 15-J-9, Folder 4)
        J.R. Worcester, construction engineer; Loop Roller Coaster Company Photomechanical print, scale 1/4” = 1’ Items is detached into two pieces: 328.3 = 17 ½” x 23 ½”, 328.4 -- 18” x 24”
      - Prescott’s Centrifugal Roller Coaster, December 15, 1900 (Box 15-J-9, Folder 4)
        J.R. Worcester, construction engineer; Loop Roller Coaster Company Photomechanical print, scale 1:32 Items is detached into two pieces: 328.1 = 17 ¼” x 24 ½”, 328.2 = 18 ¼” x 24 ½”
      - Detail of loading platform for Kid’s Coaster, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 4)
        L.A. Thompson Scenic Railway Company, The Ink on paper, 18 ½” x 30 ¾”, scale 1:24
    - Mini-rails and pleasure railroads, undated
      - Rail car, plan and elevation, undated (Box 15-J-8, Folder 10)
        Graphite and ink on paper, 29 ¾” x 18 ¼” [Soiling]
      - Mini-rail, elevation, undated (Box 15-J-8, Folder 10)
        Ink on paper, 30” x 11”
      - Mini-rail, elevation, undated (Box 15-J-8, Folder 10)
        Graphite on paper, 25 5/8” x 11”, scale 1:12 “H.S. Williams” on reverse
      - Scenic railway truck, plan and elevation, undated (Box 15-J-8, Folder 10)
        Graphite and ink on paper, 29 ¾” x 16 ½” [Foxing]
      - Mini-rail, elevation, undated (Box 15-J-8, Folder 10)
        Ink on paper, 26 ½” x 9 5/16”
      - Mini-rail, elevation, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 5)
        William F. Mangels Graphite and ink on paper, 36 1/8” x 21”
      - Mini-rail, plan and section, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 5)
        William F. Mangels Graphite and ink on paper, 36” x 19 ¾”
      - Elevation of mini-rail carriage ornamented with cherubs and musical instruments, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 5)
        “Drawing by [Marcus C.] Illions [and Sons]” Ink on paper, 31” x 22” [Minor foxing]
      - Elevation of mini-rail for Electric Railway, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 5)
        “Ben Hur, Rocky Road to Dublin, [Illegible?] Park” William F. Mangels Graphite and ink on paper, 36” x 13 ¾”
      - Mini-rail, rear and side elevation and section, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 5)
        Ink and paper, 38” x 11 1/8” [Minor foxing]
      - “Safety checks on incline,” section detail, March1912 (Box 15-J-9, Folder 6)
        William F. Mangels Ink on paper, 36” x 20 ¾”
      - Detail of track for miniature railway, section and plan, April 1911 (Box 15-J-9, Folder 6)
        William F. Mangels Ink on paper, 34 ½” x 16”, scale 1:2
      - Controller for miniature locomotive, section and plan, 1910 (Box 15-J-9, Folder 6)
        William F. Mangels Graphite and ink on paper, 33” x 10 ¾”
      - Dreamland railroad, Ryan Amusement Company, undated
        - Dreamland railroad, Ryan Amusement Company, section details of elevated track, numbers 3-15, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 7)
          William F. Mangels Ink on paper, 35 ¼” x 20 ¾”
        - Dreamland railroad, Ryan Amusement Company, section details of elevated track, numbers 16-28, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 7)
          William F. Mangels Ink on paper, 36” x 21 ½”
        - Dreamland railroad, Ryan Amusement Company, section details of elevated track, numbers 29-42, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 7)
        - Dreamland railroad, Ryan Amusement Company, section details of elevated track, numbers 43-56, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 7)
          William F. Mangels Ink on paper, 35 ½” x 19”
        - Dreamland railroad, Ryan Amusement Company, section details of elevated track, numbers 71-84, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 7)
          William F. Mangels Ink on paper, 36” x 18 ½”
        - Dreamland railroad, Ryan Amusement Company, section details of elevated track, numbers 85-98, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 7)
          William F. Mangels Graphite and ink on paper, 36” x 19 ½”
      - Palisades Park Railroad, undated
        - Palisades Park railroad, section details of elevated track, numbers 49-58, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 7)
          William F. Mangels Graphite and ink on paper, 35 ½” x 22”
        - Palisades Park railroad, section details of elevated track, numbers 59-68, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 7)
          William F. Mangels Graphite and ink on paper, 35 ½” x 22 ½”
        - Palisades Park railroad, section details of elevated track, numbers 69-80, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 7)
          William F. Mangels Graphite and ink on paper, 35 ½” x 23” [Major losses along left edge]
        - Palisades Park railroad, section details of elevated track, numbers 81-92, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 7)
        - Palisades Park railroad, section details of elevated track, numbers 1-10, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 8)
          William F. Mangels Graphite and ink on paper, 35 5/8” x 22 ¼”
        - Palisades Park railroad, section details of elevated track, numbers 13-24, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 8)
        - Palisades Park railroad, section details of elevated track, numbers 25-36, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 8)
          William F. Mangels Graphite and ink on paper, 35 ½” x 22 ¾”
        - Palisades Park railroad, section details of elevated track, numbers 37-48, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 8)
          William F. Mangels Graphite and ink on paper, 35 5/8” x 21 ¾”
        - Palisades Park railroad, section details of elevated track, numbers 93-102, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 9)
          William F. Mangels Ink on paper, 33 ½” x 21 ¾”
        - Palisades Park railroad, section details of elevated track, numbers 103-112, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 9)
          William F. Mangels Ink on paper, 32 ½” x 23 ½”
        - Palisades Park railroad, section details of elevated track, numbers, 112-125, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 9)
          William F. Mangels Ink on paper, 34 ½” x 24” [Lower left corner detached]
        - Palisades Park railroad, section details of elevated track, numbers, 127-136, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 9)
          William F. Mangels Ink on paper, 34 ½” x 24” [Brittle paper; Folded left edge May require steaming to flatten]
      - Point Breeze railroad, 1912
        - Point Breeze railroad, section details of elevated track, numbers 3-15, 1912 (Box 15-J-9, Folder 10)
          Ink on paper, 35 ½” x 24”
        - Point Breeze railroad, section details of elevated track, numbers 16-26, 1912 (Box 15-J-9, Folder 10)
          Ink on paper, 33” x 27 ½”
        - Point Breeze railroad, section details of elevated track, numbers 39-51, 1912 (Box 15-J-9, Folder 10)
          Ink on paper, 36” x 27 1/8”
        - Point Breeze railroad, section details of elevated track, numbers 52-65, 1912 (Box 15-J-9, Folder 10)
          Ink on paper, 36” x 25 ¾”
        - Point Breeze railroad, section details of elevated track, numbers 66-79, 1912 (Box 15-J-9, Folder 10)
          Ink on paper, 36” x 22 ¾”
        - Point Breeze railroad, section details of elevated track, numbers 80-103, 1912 (Box 15-J-9, Folder 10)
          Graphite and ink on paper, 36” x 19 ½”
        - Point Breeze railroad, section details of elevated track, numbers 27-38, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 11)
          William F. Mangels Graphite and ink on paper, 33 3/8” x 29 1/8”
      - Willow Grove “Coal Mine” railroad
        - Willow Grove “Coal Mine” railroad, section details of elevated track, numbers 5-20, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 11)
          William F. Mangels Graphite and ink on paper, 35 ¼” x 25 ¼”
        - Willow Grove “Coal Mine” railroad, section details of elevated track, numbers 21-34, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 11)
          William F. Mangels Graphite and ink on paper, 35 2/4” x 27”
        - 286, Willow Grove “Coal Mine” railroad, section details of elevated track, numbers 35-48, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 11)
          William F. Mangels Graphite and ink on paper, 35 ¾” x 26”
        - Willow Grove “Coal Mine” railroad, section details of elevated track, numbers 49-62, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 11)
          William F. Mangels Graphite and ink on paper, 35 5/8” x 26 3/8”
        - Willow Grove “Coal Mine” railroad, section details of elevated track, numbers 63-76, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 12)
          William F. Mangels Graphite and ink on paper, 36” x 25 ½”
        - Willow Grove “Coal Mine” railroad, section details of elevated track, numbers 77-90, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 12)
          William F. Mangels Ink on paper, 35 3/8” x 25 ¾”
        - Willow Grove “Coal Mine” railroad, section details of elevated track, numbers 91-107, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 12)
          William F. Mangels Graphite and ink on paper, 35 ½” x 25 1/8”
        - Willow Grove “Coal Mine” railroad, section details of elevated track, numbers 112-124, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 12)
          William F. Mangels Ink on paper, 36” x 26”
    - Flat Rides
      - Helter Skelter, plan, section, rear and side elevations, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 14)
        William F. Mangels Ink on paper, 34 ½” x 25”
      - Sleigh Ride, floor plan and elevation, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 14)
        Graphite and ink on paper, 40” x 30” [Edges ragged; four major tears along left edge from 4” to 12” long, some losses]
      - Sleigh Ride, plan, front and side elevations, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 14)
        William F. Mangels Ink on paper, 32 3/8” x 16 ¾”, scale 1:4
      - Sleigh Ride, foundation plan, longitudinal section, and longitudinal elevation, July 4, 1911 (Box 15-J-9, Folder 14)
        William F. Mangels Ink on paper, 65” x 31”, scale 1:96 [Detached into two pieces each approx. 32.5” long]
      - Sleigh Ride at Palisades Park, plan, cross sections, and elevation, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 14)
        William F. Mangels Graphite and ink on paper, 36” x 30”, scale ¼” =1” [Deeply creased, needs steaming to flatten appropriately, 3” tear at lower left corner and 1” tear at left edge]
      - Design for an amusement pavilion and “brakeman’s house,” plan and section, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 14)
        William F. Mangels Graphite and ink on paper, 36” x 16 ¼”
      - “Old Iron Pier, Dreamland Park,” plan of pier, elevation and section of ride car, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 14)
        William F. Mangels Ink on paper, 32 ½” x 20 ½” [Minor foxing]
      - The Tickler
        - Front elevation and plan of The Tickler pavilion, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 15)
          William F. Mangels Graphite on paper, 41 ¼” x 17 ¾”
        - Unidentified plan and elevation [of The Tickler?], undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 15)
          Graphite on paper, 43” x 14”
        - Floor plan of The Tickler, design number six, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 15)
          William F. Mangels Ink and graphite on trace, 41 2/2” x 13 3/8”, scale 1:48
        - Floor plan of The Tickler, design number nine, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 15)
          William F. Mangels Ink on paper, 41 ¾” x 14 ¾”, scale 1:48
        - Longitudinal section of The Tickler, design number nine, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 15)
          William F. Mangels Ink on paper trace, 40 ½” x 20”, scale 1:48 [Left edge ragged]
        - Longitudinal section of The Tickler, design number nine, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 15)
          William F. Mangels Ink on paper, 40 1/8” x 20 ¼”, scale 1:48
        - Longitudinal section of The Tickler, design number ten, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 15)
          William F. Mangels Ink on paper, 42” x 22 ½”, scale 1:48
        - Floor plan of The Tickler, design number twelve, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 15)
          William F. Mangels Ink on paper, 41 ½” x 15”, scale 1:48
        - Longitudinal section of The Tickler, design number twelve, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 15)
          William F. Mangels Ink on paper, 41 ¾” x 12 3/”. scale 1:48
        - Foundation plan of The Tickler, design number twelve, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 15)
          William F. Mangels Ink on paper, 41” x 15”, scale 1:48
        - Floor plan of The Tickler, design number thirteen, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 15)
          William F. Mangels Ink on paper, 41 ½” x 14 1/8”, scale 1:48
        - Foundation plan of The Tickler, design number thirteen, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 15)
          William F. Mangels Ink on paper, 41 ¼” x 22”, scale 1:48
        - Floor plan of The Tickler, design number fourteen, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 15)
          William F. Mangels Ink on paper, 41 ½”x 13 ¼”, scale 1:48
        - Floor plan of The Tickler, design number seventeen, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 15)
          William F. Mangels Ink on paper, 41 ½”x 26”, scale 1:48
        - Longitudinal section of The Tickler, design number eighteen, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 15)
          William F. Mangels Ink on paper, 41 ½”x 15 ½”, scale 1:48
        - Floor plan of The Tickler, design number eighteen, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 15)
          William F. Mangels Ink on paper, 41 1/8” x 21”, scale 1:48 [Soiling]
        - Floor plan of The Tickler, design number fifteen, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 16)
          William F. Mangels Ink on paper, 41” x 22”, scale 1:48
        - Longitudinal framing plan for The Tickler, design number five, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 16)
          William F. Mangels Ink on paper, 39” x 13”, scale 1:48
        - Ground plan of The Tickler, design number five, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 16)
          William F. Mangels Ink on paper, 39 ½” x 18”, scale 1:48
        - Floor plan of The Tickler, design number seven, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 16)
          William F. Mangels Ink on paper, 38 ¼” x 12 5/8”, scale 1:48
        - Reflected plan for The Tickler, [design number seven?,] undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 16)
          William F. Mangels Pencil on trace, 34” x 13 ½”
        - Floor plan of The Tickler, design number eight, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 16)
          William F. Mangels Ink on paper, 39 3/8” x 15 ¾”, scale 1:48 [Substantial tear along bottom right corner]
        - Floor plan of The Tickler, design number fifteen, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 16)
          Ink on paper, 35 ¾” x 11 ¾”, scale 1:48
    - Unidentified amusements and mechanical drawings, undated
      - Unidentified amusement, elevation, plan, and section detail of elevated track, undated (Box 15-J-8, Folder 11)
        Ink on paper, 21 ¾” x 28 5/8” [Medium foxing]
      - Unidentified ride, side elevation, section, and parts list, undated (Box 15-J-8, Folder 11)
        Ink on paper, 21 ¾” x 30”, scale 1:4 [Bottom edge is separated into three pieces 1” in height along the entire length; detached right corner]
      - Mechanical detail for unidentified amusement, undated (Box 15-J-8, Folder 11)
        Graphite and ink on paper, 17 ¼” x 25 ½” [Minor foxing]
      - Mechanical detail for unidentified amusement, elevation and section, undated (Box 15-J-8, Folder 11)
        Ink on paper, 22 7/8” x 20 5/8” [Minor foxing]
      - Mechanical detail for unidentified amusement, undated (Box 15-J-8, Folder 11)
        Graphite and ink on paper, 26” x 18”
      - Design for an unidentified amusement ride, floor plan and section (observe) and plan of property lot and track and elevation of rail car (reverse), undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 3)
        William F. Mangels Graphite and ink on paper, 35 ½” x 30 ¼”
      - Unidentified amusement, “measurements on a Reithoffer Machine,” section detail, undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 3)
        William F. Mangels Graphite and ink on paper, 30 ½” x 10”
      - Unidentified amusement, section detail, May 1912 (Box 15-J-9, Folder 3)
        William F. Mangels Ink on paper, 32 ½” x 17”
      - Unidentified amusement, cross section and longitudinal section, December 1910 (Box 15-J-9, Folder 3)
        William F. Mangels Ink on paper, 36” x 19 1/8”
      - Mechanical detail for unidentified amusement (obverse) and property lot plan (reverse), undated (Box 15-J-9, Folder 3)
        William F. Mangels Graphite and ink on paper, 35 ½” x 18 1/8” [Minor foxing]
      - Mechanical detail for unidentified amusement, December 1913 (Box 15-J-9, Folder 3)
        William F. Mangels Ink on paper, 20” x 31 ½”
      - Unidentified amusement, section, March1912 (Box 15-J-9, Folder 3)
        William F. Mangels Ink on paper, 30 ¼” x 15 5/8”, scale 1:48
      - Unidentified Amusements--Possibly Carousel Platforms, undated
        - Design for an unidentified ride [carousel platform?], property lot plan and section details, undated (Box 15-J-8, Folder 13)
          William F. Mangels Graphite on paper, 36” x 36”
        - Unidentified amusement [carousel platform?], section and plan, undated (Box 15-J-8, Folder 13)
          William F. Mangels Graphite and ink on paper, 41 ½” x 33 ¾”
        - Unidentified amusement [carousel platform?], plan and section details of incline and motor pit, undated (Box 15-J-8, Folder 13)
          William F. Mangels Ink on paper, 41 ½” 28 5/8”
- Series III: Personal Papers and Ephemera, 1870-2000 undated
  This series contains the personal papers, research files, and collected ephemera of Frederick Fried, all of which relates to his personal interest in the history of the amusements industry and Coney Island (Brooklyn, New York). Much of this material originally belonged to William F. Mangels and was subsequently purchased by Fried in 1955. Items include clippings, photographs, manuscripts, research files, correspondence, deeds of sale, business records, official reports, postcards, ticket stubs, and other ephemera. Researchers are advised that this series maintains its original order and related items may be founded in multiple boxes, folders, and volumes.
  - Subseries III.1: Coney Island History Papers, 1870-2000 undated
    This series contains the personal papers, research files, photographs, and collected ephemera of Frederick Fried, all of which relates to his personal interest in the history of the amusements industry and Coney Island (Brooklyn, New York). Much of this material originally belonged to William F. Mangels and was subsequently purchased by Fried in 1955. Items of especial interest include the typed manuscript and research files compiled by William F. Mangels for his book, The Outdoor Amusement Industry from Earliest Times to the Present (1952); a manuscript of “A New Era for Coney Island” by William F. Mangels; and newspaper clippings, research files, and notes by Mangels for an unpublished history of Coney Island. This series also includes business records for the W.F. Mangels Company, including catalogs and stock certificates. Other material consists of William F. Mangels’ personal seasonal passes to Palisades Amusement Park (Fort Lee, New Jersey) and other amusement parks, and, in addition, a guest book from the American Museum of Public Recreation for the years 1939-1940 with celebrity autographs from Greta Garbo, Reginald Marsh, Orson Welles, and other luminaries. This series also contains a small, discrete collection of photographs of pleasure railroads and other rides manufactured by the L.A. Thompson Scenic Railway Company, as well as photographic portraits of individuals from Coney Island’s amusements industry, such as members of the Thompson and Tilyou families, Samuel W. Gumpertz, and others. This series also contains correspondence, receipts, and other materials that detail the closing of Coney Island landmarks and Frederick Fried’s subsequent acquisition of artifacts and ephemera. Examples include receipts from the Tilyou Realty Company, a letter of authorization from Fred C. Trump, and a copy of the terms of sale of Feltman’s of Coney Island, Incorporated. Lastly, researchers may also wish to consult Frederick Fried’s “Coney Island Archive” collection report, which offers a comprehensive, descriptive inventory of each item in Frederick Fried’s original collection of artifacts, photographs, and ephemera, as well as information about the provenance of select material—a remarkable resource.
    - “Historical Review of Outdoor Amusement Industry” by William F. Mangels, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 1-2)
      Cover and typed manuscript of William F. Mangels, The Outdoor Amusement Industry from Earliest Times to the Present (New York: Vantage Press, 1952)
    - Correspondence and Research Files
      - Letter from Lawrence Heyl, Jr. to Frederick Fried, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - William F. Mangels research correspondence, 1921-1943 undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Research notes regarding Thompson, Frederick, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - “Coney Island in the Nineties” by William F. Mangels, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Feltman’s Coney Island clipping file, 1914-1915 undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
        (Clippings from various New York and Brooklyn newspapers regarding the establishment Feltman’s Coney Island (Brooklyn, New York), unbound from an unknown volume.)
      - “The Carousels of Coney Island” by Roland Summit, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - H. Takemura & Company calendar, 1939 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Photographs and clippings, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence regarding the Tilyou family, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Hand-and typewritten notes, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Manuscript of “A New Era for Coney Island” by William F. Mangels, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - William F. Mangels Papers, 1908-1955 undated
      - Photograph of the interior of main pavilion, Centennial Exhibition (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence with Leonard Schloss, 1939 (Box 12, Folder 7)
        (subjects include Frederick W. Pearce & Company, Inc., Glen Echo Park, and Gumpertz, Samuel W.)
      - Testimony of Charles N. Brewster regarding the valuation of the W.F. Mangels Company, 1908 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Photographic prints of design drawings by William F. Mangels, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
        (subjects include the cake walk, funny stairs, the "Galloping Horse Carousell," Hoopla, and roller coaster cars)
      - Typewritten labels of the “portrait gallery” and other exhibits on display in the American Museum of Public Recreation (Brooklyn, New York), undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Certificate of corporate banking resolutions and bank account agreement, W.F. Mangels Company, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Publications and catalogs, 1914-1932 undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
        (includes catalogs and product specifications issued by the W.F. Mangels Company)
      - Postcards, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Printed scan of W.F. Mangels design for mini-rail, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Empty envelope from William T. Hurley addressed to W.F. Mangels, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Stock certificates for the W.F. Mangels Company (seven items), 1908 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Stock certificate for Coney Island Carnival Company, 1919 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Brooklyn Municipal Documents, 1911-1912 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Frederick Fried and Estate of Frederick Fried papers, 1952-2000
      - Lending agreement between the Estate of Frederick Fried (Rachel Fried), Michael Immerso, and Patricia Semmel, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Receipts of purchase between Frederick Fried and Steeplechase Park/Tilyou Realty Company, 1965-1966 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Written authorization from Fred C. Trump, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Terms of sale, Feltman’s of Coney Island, Incorporated, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Engraving, “La Maisson,” undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Real estate survey of parcels in Coney Island, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 10)